Harris, Raymond and Sara; Papers apap378
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Center for the Study of Aging, 1952-2009; 4.3 cubic ft.
  - Center of Aging (7 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 7)
  - Center of Aging (8 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 8)
  - Center of Aging (9 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 9)
  - Center of Aging (10 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 10)
  - Center of Aging (11 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 11)
  - Center of Aging (12 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 12)
  - Center of Aging (13 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 13)
  - Center of Aging (14 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 14)
  - Center of Aging (15 of 15), 2005 September (Box 2, Mini-dv 15)
  - Certificate of Attendance-"Fall Prevention, Balance, Exercise and Relaxation", 2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Certificate of Incorporation, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Clinical International Conference Slow Virus, 1978 July 31 (Box 1, Cassette 4)
  - Colonie Senior Service Centers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Computer Applications in Geriatrics (1 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Cassette 5)
  - Computer Applications in Geriatrics (2 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Cassette 6)
  - Contact List, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Conversation - Sara and Richard, 1992 August 29-1992 August 30 (Box 1, Cassette 7)
  - Correspondence-William Reichel, 1995-1996; 1998; 2000; 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - CSA and Columbia Greene Community College, 1989-1991; 1994-1995; 1999; 2000-2001; 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - CSA Book Brochures, 1991; Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - CSA in the News, 1985-1986; 1998; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - CSA/IAPAAS Strategic Planning Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - CSA Newsletters, 1986; 1999-2002; 2005-2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - CSA-Photos of Gatherings, 1986; 2009; Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dialectical Behavioral Therapy in Outpatient Setting, Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Draft of Annual CSA Board Minutes, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - The Eleventh Annual Governor's Conference on Aging, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Enhancing Lifelong Health and Fitness-Exercising Body and Mind After Age 60, 2005; Undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Evaluation and Prescription for Exercise, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 8)
  - Exercise and The Good Life, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 9)
  - Exercise and The Good Life: Physical Fitness for Older Americans, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 10)
  - Fall Backup, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Minicartridge 2)
  - Fall Prevention, Balance, Relaxation, Exercise and Strength Training, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Financial Reports, 1958-1960; 1968; 1993-1995; 1997-2003; 2005 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - First International Conference "Prevention: The Key to Health for Life", 1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Fitness After Fifty, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 11)
  - Fitness After Fifty: Exercise for Health and Therapy, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Fitness After Fifty: Fitness and the Heart, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Fitness Management 2000 Source Book Update for the Trade and Professional Selection, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Fractures, Sprains, Strains and the Aged, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - General Correspondence, 1957-2006 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Geriatric News, 1989-1990; 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Geriatric and Aging, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Gerontology Society of America, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Get Ready to Exercise, 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hank Linett, 2001 March 2 (Box 1, Cassette 12)
  - Hank Linett - Relaxation Session 3, 2001 February 17 (Box 1, Cassette 13)
  - Hank - Session 3 of 4, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 14)
  - Hellenstein and Fredericks, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 15)
  - History of and Future of Physical Activity, Aging, and Sports, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Holistic Conference, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hyperextension Project, 1973-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - IAPAAS Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Income Tax Forms, 1963; 1975; 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Institutional Health (Conclu.) Exercise and The Good Life, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 16)
  - International Association of Gerontology - XI ICG. Tokyo, 1978 (Oversized 1)
  - International Association of Physical Activity, Aging, and Sports, 1995-2000; 2003; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - International Conference on Aging, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - International Conference on Rural Aging, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 17)
  - International Conference on Rural Aging - Life-Long Health and Fitness Programs to Include the Rural Elderly, 2000 June 10 (Box 1, Cassette 18)
  - International Slow Virus Meeting (1 of 4), 1978 July 31 (Box 1, Cassette 19)
  - International Slow Virus Meeting (2 of 4), 1978 July 31 (Box 1, Cassette 20)
  - International Slow Virus Meeting (3 of 4), 1979 July 31 (Box 1, Cassette 21)
  - International Slow Virus Meeting (4 of 4), 1980 July 31 (Box 1, Cassette 22)
  - Interview with Henry "Hank" Linett, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Interview with Sports Kinetics Howard and Jean Peters, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Inventory, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Johnathan Harris Grant Proposal, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Joy and Comfort Through Stretching and Relaxing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Lewis and Sophia Mumford (1 of 3), 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Lewis and Sophia Mumford (2 of 3), 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Lewis and Sophia Mumford (3 of 3), 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Lewis Mumford Interview - Transcribed (1 of 2), 1978 February 4 (Box 1, Cassette 23)
  - Lewis Mumford Interview - Transcribed (2 of 2), 1978 February 4 (Box 1, Cassette 24)
  - Lewis Mumford Interview - Transcribed, 1980 April 5 (Box 1, Cassette 25)
  - Lifelong Health and Fitness Programs to Include the Rural Elderly, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lifelong Health and Fitness-Volume I:Prevention and Human Aging, Research, Theory and Practice, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Linett BOD Minutes International Conference, 1981 May 18 (Oversized 1, Floppy-disk 2)
  - Mail Codes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Maintaining Institutional Health Through Exercise, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 26)
  - Medical Students Guide to Geriatrics, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Meeting with Marty Haase, 2001 June 11 (Box 1, Cassette 27)
  - Memo to the Long Range Planning Committee of the Society of Geriatric Cardiology, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Between the Center for the Study of Aging and Mark A. Hahn, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Merck Geriatric Cardiology research Awards, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mission Statement, 1997; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Motivation for Fitness, Undated (Box 2, Cassette 28)
  - Moving Mozart with Ann Smith, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Lewis Mumford, 1980 April 6 (Box 1, Cassette 29)
  - National Policy Study Center on Employment and Retirement, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - NCOA Meeting, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - New York State Educational Network Ready or Not Interview, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Ninth Annual Governor's Conference on Aging, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Notes, 1971; Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Officers' Certificate, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Older Americans Month-Kickoff Celebration, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The Older Woman's Project, 2001; Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Olga Hurley (1 of 2), 1986-1989; 1996; Undated; 2001-2007 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Olga Hurley (2 of 2), 1986-1989; 1996; 1998; 2001-2002; Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Olga Hurley-Accessible Buildings for People with Walking and Reaching Limitations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - On the Need for More Graduate Medical Education Programs in Geriatrics, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Oral History, Arch and History Comm. Russia Reunion, Ollie Randall, 1976 October 15 (Box 1, Cassette 30)
  - PAAS Lifetime Achievement Award-Wojtek Chodzko-Zajko P.H.D, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Pamphlet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Pep Up Your Life: A Fitness Book for Seniors, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Photograph Scrapbook, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Physical Activity, Aging and Sports-Volume II Practice, Program and Policy, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Physical Activity, Aging and Sports-Volume IV-Toward Healthy Aging: International Perspectives, 1996; Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Physical Fitness for Older American (conclusion) The Outdoor Life, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 31)
  - Planning Committees, Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Practical Organization of Programs from Physical Fitness, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 32)
  - Private Foundation Status-Internal Revenue Service, 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Program Presenters, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Publishing Contracts, 1975; 1983; 2000; 2007 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Raymond Harris (Dr.), Undated (1-inch type c 3)
  - Rehabilitation Strategies in Psychogeratrics (1 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Cassette 33)
  - Rehabilitation Strategies in Psychogeratrics (2 of 2), Undated (Box 1, Cassette 34)
  - Relaxation and Stress, 2001 September 19 (Box 1, Cassette 35)
  - Relaxation and Stress - Session 2, 2001 September 26 (Box 1, Cassette 36)
  - Report of Nominating Committee, 2001; 2006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Reports from the Executive Director, 1994-1996; 1998-2000; 2004; Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Resource Listing Report, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Richman, Undated (Box 1, Cassette 37)
  - The Role of Nutrition in the Etiology Pathogenesis and Treatment of Cardiovascular Diseases in the Elderly, Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Roy J. Shepard - Dr. Raymond Harris Memorial Reward, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - R-Ville (1 of 7), Undated (1-inch type c 4)
  - R-Ville (2 of 7), Undated (1-inch type c 5)
  - R-Ville (3 of 7), Undated (1-inch type c 6)
  - R-Ville (4 of 7), Undated (1-inch type c 7)
  - R-Ville (5 of 7), Undated (1-inch type c 8)
  - R-Ville (6 of 7), Undated (1-inch type c 9)
  - R-Ville (7 of 7), Undated (1-inch type c 10)
  - Russell Sage College, 1982 October 13 (Box 2, Cassette 38)
  - Russell Sage College, 1992 January 13 (Box 2, Cassette 39)
  - Safe Therapeutic Book Royalties, 1988-1997 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Safe Therapeutic Exercise for the Frail Elderly: An Introduction, 1995-1996; 1998; Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Safe Therapeutic Exercise for the Frail Elderly: An Introduction, Second Edition, 1989; 1996; 1999; Undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Sara and Raymond Harris at New York Hilton, 1976 October 13 (Box 2, Cassette 40)
  - Sara Harris - Abbreviated Curriculum Vitae, Undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Sara Harris Funds Advanced, Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Sara Harris Publications, 2000; 2004 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Sara Harris Speech - Russel Sage College, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Selected Critical Issues: In Aging and Special Problems of Older Women, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Selected Programs of the Center for the Studying of Aging, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Senior Citizen and Physical Fitness, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Senior Citizen Center, 1952-1954; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Senior Citizen Center - John W. Hartley, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Senior Citizen School Volunteer Program: A Manual For Program Implementation, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Slow Virus, 1978 July 31 (Box 2, Cassette 41)
  - Springfield, Undated (Box 2, Cassette 42)
  - Stop Memory Loss: How to Fight Forgetfulness Over Forty, Undated (Box 2, Cassette 43)
  - Strategic Plan, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - SuperShow Infomercial Loop Revised, 1996 May 21 (Oversized 1, Vhs 1)
  - Survey of Virginia and California Senior Athletes Training and Injury Histories, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tape #1, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Minicartridge 3)
  - Tape #2, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Minicartridge 4)
  - Tenth Annual Fitness After Fifty Workshop Conference Exercise for Health and Therapy, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Therapeutic Uses of Oral History Techniques in Medicine, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Third Annual Capital District Conference on Aging, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Third Annual National Senior Health and Fitness Day, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Topics in Aging Exercise For the Aged, Undated (Box 2, Cassette 44)
  - Town of Colonie Senior Resources Department, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Untitled, 1999 (Box 2, Minicartridge 5)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 2, Cassette 45)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box 2, Cassette 46)
  - Utilizing A Standardized Questionnaire to Identify Patients with Familial Cancer in a Minority Population, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Virgil Thompson Event - Sunday Sonata at the Nursing Home, 1982 March 28 (Box 2, Cassette 47)
  - Walking Manual, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - WGY - Raymond Harris, 1982 April 13 (Box 2, Cassette 48)
  - Who? Me? Exercise?-Safe Exercise for People Over 50-Sara Harris and Olga Hurley, R.P.T, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Who? Me? Exercise?-Safe Exercise for People Over Sixty-Draft, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Work and Life Magazines, 2004; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Albany Activism, 1954-1988; 2.4 cubic ft.
  This series contains documents related to the Harris's involvement in the Albany community. Both Raymond and Sara Harris were active in the Albany Area Chapter of the American Red Cross and the Democratic Party in Albany. Sara Harris also sat on the Board of the Directors of the Albany Inter-Racial Council which provided services like a day care center, a pool, and a community center to the people in the Arbor Hill neighborhood. Included in the series is correspondence with members of these organizations, documents demonstrating the racial injustices that the Interracial Council fought against, Arbor Hill Community Center records, and information about the Albany community at large.
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Ann Lee Hospital, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross -Annual Dinner, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Application for Service in the Home, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Board of Director-Acceptance, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Albany - Area Chapter American Red Cross - Board of Directors Meeting, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Chapter Services, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Community Resources and the Friendly Visiting Service, 1962; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Albany - Area Chapter American Red Cross - Current Activities of the Chairman of the Friendly Visiting Service, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Discussion on Recruitment - Dr. Edward Sobol, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Education and Training committee, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Friendly Home Visiting Recruitment Questionnaire, 1962; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Friendly Services Executive Committee, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Friendly Visiting Service Duties of Unite Chairman, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Friendly Visiting Service Executive Meeting Minutes, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Friendly Visiting Service - Schedule of Questions, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Friendly Visitor Unit -Project Plan, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross in the News, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross -The Lonely Grim and Gray, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Monthly Bulletin, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Mr. S - Director of the Jewish Social Service Speech Announcement, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - News Releases, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Notes, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Orientation Program, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Problems, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Questionnaire for Annual Report, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross -Record Keeping Procedure, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross -Gray Lady in a Welfare Home for the Aging, 1960; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Reminders for Volunteers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Service Budget, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Shut-in Training, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Some Thoughts on Nursing Home Visits, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Supporting Services Meeting, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Training Program for Friendly Visiting Services, 1958; 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - Villa Many Guild, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Albany - Area Chapter - American Red Cross - World Wide Red Cross Centennial Rally and Pageant, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Albany Association of the Blind -"Services for the Blind" Panel, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Albany Association of the Blind - Workshop on Preservation of Vision in Older Persons, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Albany Council of Churches Development Corporation, 1964; 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Albany Council of United Church Women, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Albany Interracial Council - 45th Annual Meeting, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Achievement Program and Buffet Supper, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Action Program for the Ross Stevens Day Care Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Activity Figures, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Agreement with the Clinton Square Neighborhood Association, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Albany Interracial Council - The Albany High School Crisis, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Albany State EOP, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Albany Youth Work Service Project, Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Annual Christmas Ball, 1960 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Annual Christmas Dance, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Annual Harvest Day Dinner, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Annual Mothers' Day Tea, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Annual Report, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Application for Workable Program Recertification, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Children's Calendar-Project Drawn by Art Class Children, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Committees, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Executive Directors, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center-Looking for an Investment?, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Opening Announcement, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Pamphlet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Program Focus, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Programs, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Repairs, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Souvenir Journal Announcement, Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Community Center Swimming Pool, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Playground, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Arbor Hill Thrifty Store Operations Report, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Athletic Committee, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Atlanta Jewish Community Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Award Dinners, 1958; 1961-1963; 1970; 1972 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Albany Interracial Council - "A Better World", 1961 December 24 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Board Manual, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Board of Directors Amendments and Policies, 1960; 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Board of Directors-Contact List, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes (1 of 2), 1957-1963; 1967; 1970-1972; 1974 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes (2 of 2), 1957-1963; 1967; 1970-1972; 1974 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Boys and Girls Program, Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Building Committee Meeting, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Business Men's Hours, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Calendars, 1958-1962; 1965; Undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Career Day Conference, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Albany Interracial Council - The Center Players, 1957 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Certificate of Incorporation of Rose-Stevens Day-Care .Inc., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Clinton Square Neighborhood Association Staff, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Community Chest Agency Problem, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Constitutions and Procedures (1 of 2), 1958-1963; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Constitutions and Procedures (2 of 2), 1958-1963; 1970 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Contact: A Newsletter Published by the Arbor Hill Community Center, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Cook for Daycare Center, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Correspondence, 1960-1963; 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Correspondence - President Mae Douglas, 1959; 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Albany Interracial Center - Council of Community Services-Tri-Agency Study Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Advisory Committee Acceptance, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Budget of Income and Expense, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Committee, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Description of Positions, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Documents Required by the State for a Permit, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Employment Inquiry-Mrs. H. E. Shackelford, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Albany Interracial Council - Daycare Center Enrollment, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)